Full Stack Software Developer UX | UI Designer

SKILLS -

HARD SKILLS:

- Programming proficiency
- Software design & testing
- Coding Excellence
- Debugging expertise
- Integration & scalability
- Front-End Build Tools
- AJAX/RESTful APIs

DEVELOPMENT PRACTICES:

- Responsive Design
 - Mobile-first approach
 - Media queries
- Version Control
- Web Programming

INTERPERSONAL PROFICIENCIES:

- Communication
- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Conflict Resolution
- Time Management Excellence
- Self-Motivated
- Relationship Building

CONTACT -



carolwargo.dev@gmail.com



(443)771-1726



github/carolwargo.com

WEBSITE

- Follow the link below to view in entirety...

- Or follow the individual CTION LINKS" provided below...
 - see my
 - view my

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate Full-Stack Software Developer with a solid foundation in both front-end and back-end technologies. I enjoy working with the latest tools and frameworks to bring new ideas to life. From crafting interactive user interfaces to designing efficient and secure server-side solutions, I am dedicated to delivering a seamless user experience while optimizing performance."

EDUCATION

George Washington University I Boot Camp

1/2023-8/2023

Certificate Program

Full Stack Software Development

Scrimba

6/2023

Learn React

13 hour course

Scrimba

7/2023

React-Router 6

19 hour course (application code link in portfolio site)

TECHNOLOGY PROFICIENCIES

Core Technologies

HTML, CSS, JavaScript,

Front End Development

React.js, React Router 6

Back End Development

Node, Express, NPM, Graph QL

Database

Mongo DB, My SQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Designer | Developer | Media manager INDEPENDENT CONTRACTOR I CONSULTANT

2019-CURRENT

Manage & maintain site to ensure a functional, up-to-date, and user-

- friendly UI.
- Implement design changes to improve appearance and user experience. Conduct audits to identify and fix any technical issues or broken links.
- Implement SEO strategies to improve search engine rankings & increase site traffic.
- · Monitor site security for threats & vulnerabilities.
- Collaborate with teams to create and upload engaging content.
- Respond to client to address user inquiries and feedback.

Real Estate Agent/Investigator

2003-CURRENT

INDEPENDENT CONTRACTOR

- Employ marketing strategies to include digital campaigns to promote people & properties.
- Analyze current & past market trends and current & future design trends.
- · Write, edit & negotiate contracts.
- · Facilitate inspections, appraisals & legal matters.
- Maintain open communication with clients and affiliates, while maintaining the high ethical standards expected at all times.
- Oversee home staging and architectural Design.
- Anticipate need through pro-active thought & planning.